Besides the current price of a particular stock.
除了特定股票的当前价格之外
Another metric that traders liked to keep an eye on is the number
交易者喜欢关注的另一个指标是
of shares that are being traded over a period of time known as volume.
在一定时间段内交易的股数 称为成交量
Often shown along the bottom of an OHLC chart.
成交量通常显示在 OHLC 图表的底部
The sum of unit price times volume gives you
成交量乘以单位股价的结果
a more accurate measure of the total amount of money moving around.
能够更准确地衡量总的流动金额
Volume is also important because it can affect how sharply its price might rise or fall.
成交量还会影响到价格的上升或下跌幅度
Let's take a look at an example.
举个例子
Acme Inc is trading at $100 per share.
ACME 的每股价格是 100 美元
Several investors speculate that Acme is going to launch
多位投资者推测 ACME 将推出一款新产品
a new product and expecting the new product to increase Acme's value significantly,
并且预计这款新产品会大大提升 ACME 的市值
they place large orders to buy a total of 100,000 shares.
他们下了大单 总共买入 100,000 股
The action of buying the shares increases the apparent demand for the stock
买入股票会提高该股票的表观需求
and consequently the price jumps to $120 per share.
导致股价飙升到 120 美元/股
That is, someone actually buys the shares at $120.
也就是有人以 120 美元买入
Why does it jump? Because there are more people who
为何会飙升？因为想要买入该股票的人
want to buy the stock than those who want to sell.
比想要卖出该股票的人多
So, the sellers can charge a premium and you bet they do.
所以卖方可以要求溢价 他们当然会这么做
Let's assume that over the next few days there aren't
假设在接下来的几天内 ACME 没有推出任何产品
any announcements and no significant new activity in Acme's stock.
他们的股票没有任何大的变动
Some shareholders want to pull out their money
某些股东想要撤出资金
and invest in another opportunity they hear about.
并投资他们听到的其他投资机会
So the price begins to fall gradually.
所以价格逐渐下跌
Noticing this trend other investors decide to sell the majority of shares they bought.
注意这个走势 其他投资者决定卖出他们购买的大量股票
So that they can make a profit while the price is still high.
从而在股价依然很高时获利
As expected, this results in a sharp drop in
不出所料 ACME 的股价开始下跌
Acme's stock price it comes down to $90 per share.
跌倒 90 美元/股
If you're monitoring the price and volume of Acme's stock,
如果你观察 ACME 股票的价格和成交量
you might have noticed the relationship between volume of transactions and price changes.
可能会发现成交量与价格变化之间的关系
In general, large volumes of buy orders tend to sharply increase
通常 大批量的买单一般会导致股价飙升
the stock price and large volumes of sell orders make it fall.
大批量的卖单会导致股价下跌
This is another signal that you can use to decide when to trade a given stock.
你可以利用这个信号判断何时交易股票
It is also something to keep in mind if you're
如果你是大型投资者并且交易大量股票
a major investor and you trade in large volumes.
也需要注意这一点
Some hedge funds for instance will spread their transactions over multiple days,
例如 某些对冲基金会将他们的交易分布到多天
so that their own actions don't end up affecting the price adversely.
这样他们自己的操作就不会对价格造成不利影响
Note that the volume of transactions also varies throughout any trading day.
注意 成交量在任何一个交易日内都会变化
This is something to be aware of if you want to use volume as a trading signal.
如果你想将成交量当做交易信号 需要注意这一点
Stocks that are of active interest will
备受关注的股票
typically see a lot of training at the beginning of the day.
通常在开盘时交易量很高
Since that is when traders get to act on,
因为这时候交易者
all the new information gathered and analyzed since the previous day's market close.
会分析从前一天收盘时收集的数据并采取行动
This initial activity known as price discovery,
这种初始行为称为价格发现
helps buyers and sellers converge on a mutually acceptable market price for each stock.
有助于买方和卖方就每个股票达成可接受的市价
Then the volume falls to a lower level as typical daily trading activity resumes.
然后 恢复典型的一天交易活动 成交量开始下降
Finally, towards the end of the trading day,
最后 在交易日结束前
activity tends to increase a little resulting in a higher volume.
交易活动稍微上升 导致成交量上升
This can be due to several reasons including day traders who want to close out
原因有很多 例如当日交易者想要平仓
any open positions and funds that typically update their holdings at the end of the day.
并且基金通常会在一天结束时更新他们的持股情况
In fact, some traders who have decided to buy-sell particular stocks,
实际上 某些决定买卖特定股票的交易者
may not want to risk waiting for the next day.
可能不想冒着等到第二天的风险
Who knows what events might take place in the meantime and how they might affect prices.
谁知道在这个过程中可能会发生什么并如何影响股价
Volume carries a lot of information about a stock and is an often overlooked metric.
成交量包含很多股票信息 通常是被忽略的指标
High volume trade, is more likely to affect the price of a stock than a low volume trade.
高成交量比低成交量更有可能影响到股价
Therefore, volume is an important factor to consider within your trading strategy.
所以 成交量是重要的交易策略考虑因素